clutchmagonline.com 2014-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Clutch Magazine

This privacy statement covers the Sutton New Media LLC sites (Clutch Magazine Online and Coco & Crème). Please read this statement carefully before using proceeding to access Sutton New Media LLC sites. Your use of Sutton New Media LLC sites indicates your agreement to abide by the terms in effect.

**Information Collection**  
Sutton New Media LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on the Sutton New Media LLC site. Sutton New Media LLC may collect information from our users at several different points on the Sutton New Media LLC site.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the Sutton New Media LLC sites, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. If a third party complains that a comment breaches our **Terms of Service** (e.g. libels them), then in accordance with our Terms, we will make reasonable efforts to contact the commenter and alert them to the situation. If we are required to by law to disclose commenters’ contact information, we will attempt to contact commenter to give them the opportunity to respond to such requests. Please refer to our Terms of Use for more information.

**Mailing List**  
Sutton New Media LLC may launch a mailing list for our site. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site and possibly emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you through trusted Web advertising partners. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, is used to serve ads to you.

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Sutton New Media LLC may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the Sutton New Media LLC site.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event Sutton New Media LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**  
The Sutton New Media LLC sites contain links to other site. Please be aware that Sutton New Media LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Sutton New Media LLC.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Sutton New Media LLC has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Sutton New Media LLC only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by trusted Web advertising partners, among other services. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever Sutton New Media LLC changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at **privacy@clutchmagonline.com**

style="display:inline-block;width:300px;height:250px"  
data-ad-client="ca-pub-4490002161143424"  
data-ad-slot="9293572801">
